Jinwang.
Master.
Brother Qingxuan.
Hahaha.
I underestimated you.
You really descended to the mortal realm and became a demon.
Not exactly a demon,
just seeking freedom.
Master,
you know each other?
I didn't expect
you to fall this low.
Fall?
High Immortal,
have you not fallen as well?
Back then,
I looked up to you so much.
My descent to the mortal realm
is the will of Heaven.
Then my descent
is to break the will of Heaven.
You don't think
that by severing my immortal root,
you can defeat me, do you?
I'm not that overconfident.
But
to take you away,
I have many other ways.
Master, save me!
Master!
Let the child go.
I'll go with you.
Don't treat me like a three-year-old.
If you want to save your disciple,
we'll meet at Tushan.
Ancestor!
That demoness had it planned all along.
I didn't catch them.
They got away.
Save the people first.
A single thought of gods and buddhas saves all beings.
A single thought of demonic obsession throws the universe into chaos.
Save others and yourself with compassion.
When you comprehend the true path of your heart again,
you may return to the immortal path
and ascend the cloud steps once more.
Brother Qingxuan,
when are we going to save Feilu?
When did I say I was going to save him?
What did you say?
Since those demons have left,
I assume they won't return.
The officials from the Sitian Bureau
should also be on their way here.
My entanglement with Ercheng ends here.
As soon as day breaks,
I will take my leave.
Immortal, you've saved Ercheng many times.
It's not too late to leave after we present you with a small gift.
Yes.
No need.
I've been a bit tired lately.
Prepare a horse for me.
But...
Just do as I say.
And you,
don't follow me anymore.
Hey!
You don't care about Feilu anymore?
He was taken because of you.
My immortal body has been severed,
my form is broken.
Even if I go to Tushan in person,
it would be a waste of effort.
In this world,
I still have unfinished business.
As for Feilu,
he will have to rely on his own destiny.
You!
Feilu also calls you Master.
I never said I would accept him as a disciple.
Just like Hu San calling me Ancestor,
it's just wishful thinking on their part.
As for you,
you're just a tree demon.
If I wanted to subdue you,
you wouldn't last three moves.
Considering you've helped the people along the way
and haven't done any more evil deeds,
I'll spare you for now.
If you bother me again,
I will not spare you.
What Golden Immortal?
You're just a coward who clings to life and fears death!
Immortal, you saved Ercheng.
We are deeply grateful
and have come to see you off.
However, most of the people are still healing.
They cannot come to see you off.
Please do not be offended.
Please accept our bow.
The seven human emotions
cause all kinds of suffering,
which are hard to control.
I hope you will behave yourselves from now on.
Do not make any more mistakes.
Yes, yes.
Thank you, Immortal. Thank you.
The bearing of an immortal
is indeed extraordinary.
County Magistrate,
why don't we submit a petition
to change the name of Ercheng to Xuancheng?
What do you think?
Excellent.
Absolutely excellent.
What are you doing?
I saved a lot of people.
Have you ever seen him ride a horse before?
No.
He's always traveled on foot.
I thought Golden Immortals could fly.
That's called riding the wind.
What do you mean, fly?
Wait a minute.
He's never even ridden a horse before.
Don't you think that's strange?
Didn't he say he was a bit tired?
With his powers,
even if his immortal roots were severed,
he never had the habit of riding horses.
The martial world is so big.
He could just walk and travel slowly.
When things are out of the ordinary,
there must be something fishy going on.
I noticed that you
are prejudiced against demons.
Look at the direction he's heading.
It's toward Tushan.
He's going to save Feilu.
Tushan is where the demons of the Tushan clan gather.
He must be afraid of implicating us,
so he decided to go alone.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
To save Feilu.
Why are you still following me?
Ping Jie Qiang Hai Hui.
Jie Qiang Hai.